(BOTH YELLING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Well struck.
Well struck. dog.
Did you like that?
It was well struck.
Your Grace.
I already said
it was well struck.
Yes. Your Grace.
Who's next?
HERALD: Lothor Brune.
freerider in the service
of Lord Baelish.
Ser Dontos the Red
of House Hollard.
of House Hollard!
DONTOS: Here I am.
Here I am.
Sorry. Your Grace.
My deepest apologies.
JOFFREY: Are you drunk?
No.
No. No. Your Grace.
I had two cups of wine.
Two cups?
That's not much at all.
Please. have another cup.
Are you sure. Your Grace?
Yes. To celebrate
my name day.
Have two.
Have as much as you like.
I would be honored.
Your Grace.
Ser Meryn. help Ser Dontos
celebrate my name day.
See that
he drinks his fill.
(CROWD GASPS)
(GURGLING)
You can't.
What did you say?
Did you say I can't?
I only meant
it would be bad luck
to kill a man
on your name day.
What kind of stupid
peasant's superstition...
HOUND:
The girl is right.
What a man sows
on his name day.
he reaps all year.
(MEN LAUGHING)
(WINE POURING)
(SIGHS)
Take him away.
I'll have him killed
tomorrow. the fool.
(CROWD MURMURING)
He is a fool.
You're so clever
to see it.
He'll make a much better
fool than a knight.
He doesn't deserve
the mercy of a quick death.
Did you hear my lady.
Ser Dontos?
From this day.
you'll be my new fool.
Thank you. Your Grace.
And you. my lady.
thank you.
TYRION: Beloved nephew.
We looked for you
on the battlefield.
You were nowhere
to be found.
I've been here.
ruling the kingdoms.
What a fine job
you've done.
Look at you.
More beautiful than ever.
And you!
You're going to be
bigger than the Hound.
but much better looking.
(LAUGHS)
This one
doesn't like me.
Can't imagine why.
We heard you were dead.
I'm glad
you're not dead.
Me. too. dear.
Death is so boring.
especially now.
with so much excitement
in the world.
My lady.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Her loss?
Her father was
a confessed traitor.
But still her father.
Surely. having so recently
lost your own beloved father.
you can sympathize.
My father was a traitor.
My mother and brother
are traitors. too.
I am loyal to my
beloved Joffrey.
Of course you are.
Well. enjoy your name day.
Your Grace.
Wish I could stay
and celebrate.
but there is work
to be done.
What work?
Why are you here?
PYCELLE: A raven
arrived from the citadel
this morning. Your Grace.
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
The conclave has met.
considered reports
from maesters all over
the Seven Kingdoms.
and declared
this great summer
done at last.
The longest summer
in living memory.
The peasants say.
a long summer means
an even longer winter.
PYCELLE:
A common superstition.
LITTLEFINGER:
We have enough wheat
for a five-year winter.
If it lasts any longer.
we'll have fewer peasants.
The city's drowning
in refugees. Your Grace.
fleeing the war.
We have nowhere
to house them.
And with winter coming.
it'll only get worse.
You command the city watch.
do you not. Lord Slynt?
I do. Your Grace.
And are you not a lord
at my command?
I owe my title and lands
to your generosity.
Your Grace.
Then do your job.
Shut the gates
to the peasants.
They belong in the field.
not our capital.
Yes. Your Grace.
(TYRION WHISTLING TUNE)
Don't get up.
More ravishing than ever.
big sister.
War agrees with you.
Forgive the interruption.
Carry on.
What are you doing here?
It's been
a remarkable journey.
I pissed off
the edge of the Wall.
I slept in a sky cell.
I fought with
the hill tribes.
So many adventures.
so much to be thankful for.
What are you doing here?
This is the small council.
Yes. well. I do believe
the Hand of the King
is welcome
at all small
council meetings.
Our father is
Hand of the King.
Yes. but in his absence...
VARYS: Your father
has named Lord Tyrion
to serve as hand
in his stead
while he fights.
Out! All of you out!
I would like to know
how you tricked Father
into this.
If I were capable
of tricking Father.
I'd be emperor of
the world by now.
You brought this
on yourself.
I've done nothing.
Quite right.
you did nothing
when your son called
for Ned Stark's head.
Now the entire North
has risen up against us.
I tried to stop it.
Did you? You failed.
That bit of theater
will haunt our family
for a generation.
Robb Stark is a child.
Who's won every battle
he's fought.
Do you understand
we're losing the war?
What do you know
about warfare?
Nothing.
But I know people.
And I know that our
enemies hate each other
almost as much as
they hate us.
Joffrey is king.
You are here
to advise him.
I'm only here
And if the king
listens to what I say.
the king might just get
his Uncle Jaime back.
How?
You love your children.
It's your
one redeeming quality.
That and your cheekbones.
The Starks love
their children as well.
And we have
two of them.
One.
One?
Arya. little animal.
she disappeared.
Disappeared? What.
in a puff of smoke?
We had three Starks
to trade.
You chopped one's head off
and let another escape.
Father will be furious.
It must be odd for you
to be
the disappointing child.
LEADRANACH:
My lord. may the old gods
watch over your brother
and all our Northern sons.
The walls of my holdfast
will not stand the winter.
The stones were last
mortared in the time
of King Aerys.
and I'm afraid
the masons today
are not fit to carry
their fathers' hammers.
When I was a boy.
I remember seeing them
put up a new tower
at Torrhen's Square
in a summer.
Men worked back then.
Today. my holdfast
looks like it was built
by drunk children.
At night you can hear
the wind howling
through the gaps.
Gods forbid it rains.
Why. I might as well
sleep beneath a waterfall.
Maintenance of a holdfast
generally falls to the lord
of that holdfast.
Generally. yes.
but I've sent
all the young men off
to fight Robb Stark's war.
King Robb.
And it's not his war.
He didn't choose it.
Maybe not. my lord.
but he called in his
banners and took the men.
Joffrey killed my father.
your liege lord.
Do you remember
your vows. ser?
Of course I remember!
We can spare four masons
for a week. my lord.
Will that be sufficient
to repair your walls?
I believe it will.
We didn't want him here
all day. did we?
I didn't like the way
he was talking about Robb.
Nor did I.
But listening to people
you'd rather not listen to
is one of your
responsibilities
as Lord of Winterfell.
(BRAN SIGHS)
Lord Portan.
My lord. may the old gods
watch over your brother
and all our
Northern sons.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(WINGS FLAPPING)
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
Boil this for an hour
and drink the tea.
Makes all your
pain go away.
BRAN:
Don't have any pain.
Lucky for you.
That way.
You've been having
those dreams again.
BRAN: I don't dream.
Everyone dreams.
I don't.
Heard some of the men
talking about the comet.
They say it's an omen.
They say it means Robb
will win a great victory
in the South.
Did they?
I heard some other fools say
it's Lannister Red.
Means the Lannisters
will rule all Seven
Kingdoms before long.
Heard a stable boy say
it's the color of blood
to mark the death
of your father.
The stars don't
fall for men.
Red comet means
one thing. boy.
Dragons.
The dragons are all dead.
They've been dead
for centuries.
(SHRIEKS)
Mmm.
What did your brother say
about them. Khaleesi?
He said they ate meat.
He didn't tell you
what kind of meat?
My brother didn't know
anything about dragons.
He didn't know
anything about anything.
Eh.
(WHINNIES)
(WOMEN MURMURING)
She was Drogo's
first gift to me.
I remember.
I promised
to protect them.
Promised them
their enemies
would die screaming.
How do I make
starvation scream?
A trick I never learned.
I'm afraid.
Does it ever end?
This is further east
than I've ever been.
But. yes. Khaleesi.
everything ends.
even the Red Waste.
And you're sure
there's no other way?
If we go south
to the land of
the Lhazareen.
the Lamb Men will kill us
and take your dragons.
If we go west to
the Dothraki Sea.
the first khalasar we meet
will kill us and take
your dragons.
No one will
take my dragons.
They are too weak to fight.
as are your people.
You must be their strength.
As you are mine.
(SPEAKS DOTHRAKI)
Rakharo.
You never have.
This is bad time to start.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(WIND HOWLING)
Having a rough time of it?
Nothing's killed me yet.
GRENN: Your arse
killed the sledge.
You offered me a ride.
I just wanted you
to shut up about
your damn blisters.
I was born in a place
like this.
Later. I fell
on hard times.
SAMWELL: Are those girls?
DOLOROUS EDD:
Craster's daughters.
I haven't seen a girl
in six months.
I'd keep on
not seeing them
if I were you.
What. he don't like people
messing with his daughters?
He don't like people
messing with his wives.
He marries his daughters.
and they give him
more daughters.
And on and on it goes.
That's foul.
It's beyond foul.
All the other wildlings
for a hundred leagues
have disappeared.
Craster's still here.
He must be doing
something right.
What happens
to the boys?
Hmm?
He marries
his daughters.
What does he do
with his sons?
He said he planned
to stop here on his way
to the Frostfangs.
People make all
sorts of plans.
I haven't seen Benjen Stark
in three years.
Haven't missed him.
Always treated me
like scum.
Haven't had any good
wine for a long time.
You Southerners
make good wine.
I'll give you that.
We're not Southerners.
Who's this little girl?
You're prettier
than half my daughters.
You got a nice wet twat
between your legs?
What's your name?
Jon Snow.
Snow. eh?
Listen to me. bastard.
All you lot from
south of the Wall.
you're Southerners.
But now you're
in the North.
the real North.
The lad meant no harm.
I catch that
pretty little bastard
talking to my daughters...
No one will talk
to your daughters.
you have my word.
Now. sit down
and shut your mouth.
You bring any of that
good wine with you?
We did.
We passed through
six villages
on the way here.
All six were abandoned.
Where have all
the wildlings gone?
I could tell you.
but I'm thirsty.
MORMONT: There's
a barrel of Dornish wine
on the sledge.
Bring it in here.
MAN: Yes. Commander.
CRASTER: You want to know
where they've all gone?
North. to join up
with Mance Rayder.
Your old friend.
He's no friend of mine.
He broke his vows.
betrayed his brothers.
Aye.
But once he was
just a poor black crow.
And now he's
King-beyond-the-Wall.
He's been calling
himself that for years.
What's he king of?
A frozen lake somewhere?
That's a good-looking ax.
Fresh forged?
Give it here.
You'll have another one
made at Castle Black.
Here.
That's some
lovely steel.
You want to know what
Mance Rayder is doing?
Gathering an army.
What I hear. he's already
got more men than any of
your Southern Kings.
And where does he plan
marching this army?
When you're all the way
north. there's only one
direction to go.
These are bad times to be
living alone in the wild.
The cold winds are rising.
Let them come.
My roots are sunk deep.
Wife.
tell the Lord Crow
how content we are.
This is our place.
Our husband keeps us safe.
Better to live free
than die a slave.
CRASTER: Don't it make you
jealous. old man.
to see me with
all these young wives
and you with no one
to warm your bed?
We chose different paths.
Aye. and you chose the path
with no one but boys on it.
You'll be wanting to sleep
beneath my roof. I suppose.
and eat me out of pigs.
A roof would be welcome.
It's been hard riding.
We've brought our own food
and good steel for you.
Any man lays a hand
on one of my wives.
he loses the hand.
And I see this one
staring too long.
I might just
gouge his eyes out.
Your roof. your rules.
(GRUNTS)
Who am I?
Lord Commander.
And who are you?
Jon Snow.
Who are you?
Your steward.
You want to
lead one day?
Then learn
how to follow.
(MAN PANTING)
MELISANDRE: Lord of Light.
come to us in our darkness.
We offer you
these false gods.
Take them and cast
your light upon us.
for the night is dark
and full of terrors.
MEN: For the night is dark
MELISANDRE:
After the long summer.
darkness will fall
heavy on the world.
The stars will bleed.
We need to stop her.
MELISANDRE:
The cold breath of winter
will freeze the seas...
Not now.
...and the dead
shall rise in the North.
All you men were named
in the light of the Seven!
Is this how you treat
the gods of your fathers?
Are you so eager to
spit on your ancestors?
You smell of fear.
fear and piss
and old bones.
Do you want to stop me?
Stop me.
In the ancient books.
it's written
that a warrior will draw
a burning sword
from the fire.
And that sword
shall be Lightbringer.
Stannis Baratheon.
Warrior of Light.
your sword awaits you.
(MEN CHEERING)
MEN: Lord.
cast your light upon us!
MELISANDRE:
For the night is dark
and full of terrors.
and full of terror.
This woman will lead him
into a war he cannot win.
Stannis is our king.
We follow
where he leads.
even if we don't
like the path.
King.
Since that boar killed
his brother. every lord
wants a coronation.
I don't serve the others.
I serve Stannis.
As do I.
but loyal service
means telling hard truths.
He's surrounded by
fools and fanatics.
but he trusts you. Davos.
If you tell him
the truth...
What's the truth?
MATTHOS: "And I declare upon
the honor of my house that
my beloved brother Robert..."
He wasn't my
beloved brother.
I didn't love him.
He didn't love me.
A harmless courtesy.
Your Grace.
A lie. Take it out.
"That my brother Robert
left no trueborn heirs.
"the boy Joffrey.
the boy Tommen.
"and the girl Myrcella
being born of incest
"between Cersei Lannister
and her brother
Jaime Lannister.
"By right of birth..."
the Kingslayer.
Call him what he is.
"And her brother
Jaime Lannister.
the Kingslayer."
"By right of birth and blood.
I do this day lay claim..."
STANNIS: Make it
Ser Jaime Lannister.
the Kingslayer.
Whatever else he is.
the man's still a knight.
"Ser Jaime Lannister.
the Kingslayer.
"By right of birth
and blood.
"I do this day lay claim
to the Iron Throne
of Westeros.
"Let all true men
declare their loyalty."
When Eddard Stark learned
the truth. he told only me.
I'll not make
the same mistake.
Send copies of that letter
to every corner of the realm.
from the Arbor to the Wall.
The time has
come to choose.
Let no man claim
ignorance as an excuse.
Your Grace.
the Lannisters
are the true enemy.
If. for the time being.
you could make peace
with your brother...
I'll not make peace
with Renly while he
calls himself king.
Well. many have
already declared for him.
Mace Tyrell.
Randyll Tarly.
Stannis does not need
to beg this lord or
that lord for support.
The Lord of Light
stands behind him.
And how many ships
has the Lord of Light
got in his fleet?
He has no need for ships.
DAVOS:
I'm sure he doesn't.
but we do if
we're going to war.
If not Renly. Your Grace.
join forces with Robb Stark.
Who would steal
the northern half
of my kingdom.
I've always served thieves
according to their deserts.
as you well know. Ser Davos.
Joffrey. Renly. Robb Stark.
they're all thieves.
They'll bend the knee
or I'll destroy them.
I owe you an apology.
my king.
My duty is to serve.
You have chosen the new god
over the old gods.
May the Lord of Light
watch over us all.
Shall we drink together?
Don't.
A cup of wine to honor
the one true god.
(THUDS)
(MEN MURMURING)
The night is dark
and full of terrors.
old man.
but the fire
burns them all away.
(CHATTER)
King in the North.
I keep expecting you
to leave me in one castle
or another for safekeeping.
but you drag me along
from camp to camp.
Have you grown
fond of me. Stark?
Is that it?
I've never seen you
with a girl.
If I left you with
one of my bannermen.
your father would know
within a fortnight
and my bannerman
would receive a raven
with a message.
"Release my son
and you'll be rich
beyond your dreams.
"Refuse and your house
will be destroyed.
root and stem."
You don't trust the loyalty
of the men following you
into battle?
Oh. I trust them
with my life.
just not with yours.
Smart boy.
What's wrong?
Don't like being
called "boy"?
Insulted?
(GREY WIND SNARLING)
ROBB: You insult yourself.
Kingslayer.
You've been
defeated by a boy.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
You're held captive
by a boy.
Perhaps you'll be
killed by a boy.
Stannis Baratheon
sent ravens to all the
high lords of Westeros.
King Joffrey Baratheon
is neither a true king
nor a true Baratheon.
He's your bastard son.
If that's true.
Stannis is the
rightful king.
How convenient for him.
My father learned
the truth.
That's why you
had him executed.
I was your prisoner
when Ned Stark
lost his head.
Your son killed him
so the world wouldn't
learn who fathered him.
And you.
you pushed my brother
from a window because
he saw you with the queen.
You have proof?
Or do you want
to trade gossip like
a couple of fishwives?
I'm sending one of
your cousins down to King's
Landing with my peace terms.
You think
my father's going to
negotiate with you?
You don't know him
very well.
No. but he's starting
to know me.
Three victories don't
make you a conqueror.
It's better
than three defeats.
(SNARLING)
SHAE: This city stinks.
Like dead bodies.
TYRION:
A bit corpsey. yes.
And shit.
I thought you
wanted to come here.
I love it.
You love the smell of
dead bodies and shit?
And cum and garlic and rum.
You can smell cum
from the balcony?
I love the stink.
I love the noise.
Cities make me
want to fuck.
And so did the country.
(SIGHS)
This is where I belong.
Yes. well.
you need to be careful.
No one can know
you're here.
No one will know.
You can't trust anyone
in King's Landing.
They're all liars.
good liars. bad liars.
one or two great liars.
What about you?
Me? I'm not from here.
I'm a slave to the truth.
(LAUGHS) Truth?
You are the biggest
little liar I have
ever met.
Why do you think
I am so little?
I'm being crushed beneath
the weight of all that truth.
Ned Stark
actually slept on this.
As if the poor man
didn't suffer enough.
One of the many changes
we'll have to make
around here.
Lord Baelish.
Your Grace.
I wonder if I might
ask you for a favor.
Of course. Your Grace.
Ned Stark's
youngest daughter Arya.
we can't seem
to locate her.
If she's escaped the capital.
Winterfell seems
the logical destination.
And yet my friends
in the North report
no sign of her.
Curious.
If we choose
to negotiate
with the Starks.
the girl has some value.
Whoever finds her...
Well. you know
what they say about
Lannisters and debts.
Well. you could ask
Varys where she is.
He'll have
an answer for you.
Whether you believe it...
Myself. I have always
had a hard time
trusting eunuchs.
Who knows what they want?
A mockingbird.
You created your own sigil.
didn't you?
Yes.
Appropriate.
for a self-made man
with so many songs to sing.
I'm glad you like it.
Some people are
fortunate enough
to be born into
the right family.
Others have to
find their own way.
I heard a song once
about a boy
of modest means
who found his way
into the home of
a very prominent family.
He loved
the eldest daughter.
Sadly. she had eyes
for another.
When boys and girls
live in the same home.
awkward situations can arise.
Sometimes. I've heard.
even brothers and sisters
develop certain affections.
And when those affections
become common knowledge.
well. that is an awkward
situation indeed.
especially in
a prominent family.
But prominent families
often forget a simple truth.
I've found.
And which truth is that?
Knowledge is power.
Seize him.
Cut his throat.
Stop. Wait.
I've changed my mind.
Let him go.
Step back three paces.
Turn around.
Close your eyes.
Power is power.
Do see if you can
take some time away from
your coins and your whores
to locate
the Stark girl for me.
I would very much
appreciate it.
ROBB: You're
Ser Alton Lannister?
I am. Your Grace.
ROBB: I offer your cousins
peace if they meet my terms.
First. your family
must release my sisters.
Second. my father's bones
must be returned to us
so he may rest beside
his brother and sister
in the crypts
beneath Winterfell.
And the remains of all those
who died in his service
must also be returned.
Their families
can honor them
with proper funerals.
An honorable request.
Your Grace.
Third...
Joffrey and the Queen Regent
must renounce all claim to
dominion of the North.
From this time
till the end of time.
we are a free and
independent kingdom.
The King in the North.
King in the North.
Neither Joffrey nor any
of his men shall set foot
in our lands again.
If he disregards
this command.
he shall suffer
the same fate
as my father.
only I don't need a servant
to do my beheading for me.
These are...
Your Grace. these are...
These are my terms.
If the Queen Regent
and her son meet them.
I'll give them peace.
If not.
I will litter the South
with Lannister dead.
King Joffrey
is a Baratheon.
Your Grace.
Oh. is he?
You'll ride at daybreak.
Ser Alton.
That will be all
for tonight.
A word. Your Grace?
You don't have to
call me "Your Grace"
when no one's around.
It's not so bad
once you get used to it.
I'm glad someone's
gotten used to it.
The Lannisters are going
to reject your terms.
you know?
Of course they are.
We can fight them
in the fields
as long as you like.
but we won't beat them
until you take
King's Landing.
And we can't take
King's Landing
without ships.
My father has ships
and men who know
how to sail them.
Men who fought my father.
Men who fought King Robert
to free themselves
from the yoke of the South.
just like you're doing now.
I'm his only
living son.
He'll listen to me.
I know he will.
I'm not a Stark.
I know that.
But your father raised me
to be an honorable man.
We can avenge him
together.
You don't want
Balon Greyjoy
for an ally.
I need his ships.
They say he has 200.
They say a million rats
live in the sewers
of King's Landing.
Shall we rally them
to fight for us?
I understand
you don't trust
Lord Greyjoy.
I don't trust
Lord Greyjoy because
he is not trustworthy.
Your father had
to go to war to
end his rebellion.
Yes. And now
I'm the one rebelling
against the throne.
Before me. it was Father.
You married one rebel
and mothered another.
I mothered more
than just rebels.
a fact you seem
to have forgotten.
If I trade the Kingslayer
for two girls.
my bannermen will
string me up by my feet.
You want to leave Sansa
in the queen's hands?
And Arya...
I haven't heard
a word about Arya.
What are we fighting for.
if not for them?
It's more
complicated than that!
You know it is.
It's time for me
to go home.
I haven't seen Bran
or Rickon in months.
You can't go
to Winterfell.
I beg your pardon?
I'll send Rodrik to
watch over the boys
because tomorrow
you'll ride south
to the Stormlands.
Why in the name
of all the gods...
Because I need you
to negotiate with
Renly Baratheon.
He's rallied
an army of 100.000.
You know him.
You know his family.
I haven't seen
Renly Baratheon
since he was a boy.
You have a hundred
other lords...
Which of these lords
do I trust more than you?
If Renly sides with us.
we'll outnumber them
two to one.
When they feel the jaws
beginning to shut.
they'll sue for peace.
We'll get the girls back.
Then we'll all go home.
for good.
I will ride
at first light.
We will all be together
again soon. I promise.
You've done so well.
Your father
would be proud.
Give Lord Renly my regards.
King Renly.
There's a king
in every corner now.
What is all this?
Returning this room to
its proper appearance.
Say what you will
about the Targaryens.
they were conquerors.
That is a seat
for a conqueror.
It needs a room to match it.
not vines and flowers.
We can't find Arya Stark.
With luck. she's dead
in a ditch somewhere.
Perhaps.
But if not. we need her.
They'll never give
Jaime back to us
for Sansa alone.
I think they might.
They're weak.
They put too much value
on their women.
We need to set our armies
to the task of finding her.
Send out as many men
as we can.
I'm sure if you
asked Grandfather...
The king does not ask.
he commands.
And my grandfather's
stupidity in the field
of battle
is the reason Robb Stark
has Uncle Jaime
in the first place.
His life is in danger.
We're at war.
All our lives
are in danger.
I heard a disgusting lie
about Uncle Jaime.
And you.
Our enemies will say
anything to weaken
your claim to the throne.
It's not a claim.
The throne is mine.
Of course it is.
No one believes
this foul gossip.
Someone believes it.
Father had
other children?
Besides me and Tommen
and Myrcella?
(HAMMERS CLATTERING)
What are you asking?
I'm asking
if he fucked other women
when he grew tired of you.
How many bastards
does he have running...
(WORK STOPS)
What you just did
is punishable by death.
You will never do it again.
Never.
That will be all. Mother.
(SCREAMING)
No. no. no. no.
Do you have any idea
how ridiculous you sound?
Ease into it.
Slowly. with passion.
Oh. yeah.
Go wash yourselves.
Put some clothes on.
Both of you are
working tonight.
We do things
differently here. Daisy.
This isn't some
five-copper bawdy house
in Hayseed Hall.
Haystack Hall.
Wherever you're from.
Our establishment
doesn't cater to plowmen
and goat herders.
Lord Olsen.
Taste is everything here.
Littlefinger's
a fancy man.
Don't call him
Littlefinger.
He doesn't like it.
Lord Baelish.
She pretends she doesn't
speak the common tongue
so that people will
think she's exotic.
She grew up
just down the road
in Flea Bottom.
She's beautiful.
She's a dumb slut. really.
but a lid for every pot.
(ARMOR RATTLING)
Lord Commander.
Good to see you again.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
(DOOR BREAKS)
(PEOPLE SCREAM)
You do realize this
establishment is owned
by Lord Petyr Baelish.
the King's
Master of Coin.
Coin which goes
in many pockets.
Orders.
Whose orders?
Someone who doesn't care
what Littlefinger thinks.
(WOMAN SOBBING)
(BABY CRYING)
No. you can't.
No! Please!
No! Not my Barra!
Please. Please.
Enough. Get it done.
Kill the bastard.
WOMAN: No. no!
Please.
Give it here.
No. please.
(DAGGER SLASHES)
(SCREAMS)
MAN: Spread out.
Search every house.
Every room.
Look in every room.
(GRUNTING)
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Gendry!
His name is Gendry.
Where is the bastard?
The Night's Watch!
Please. stop!
Where?
They took him
up the Kingsroad.
heading north.
How will we know him?
He's got
a bull's head helmet.
He made it himself.
Find him.